<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Awair</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    
    
    
    
    <string name="ozone_intro">Ozone (O3) is the major harmful ingredient in smog. It is not emitted directly into the air but produced in the atmosphere when gases or vapors of organic chemicals called hydrocarbons combine with nitrogen oxide compounds in the presence of sunlight. Organic hydrocarbon gases, one of the raw ingredients of ozone, are released from a variety of sources related to human activities. Major sources include refineries, gas stations, motor vehicles, chemical plants, paints and solvents. Harmful ozone in the lower atmosphere should not be confused with ozone in the upper atmosphere, which protects us from ultraviolet radiation.\nOzone near the ground can cause a number of health problems. Ozone can lead to more frequent asthma attacks in people who have asthma and can cause sore throats, coughs, and breathing difficulty. It may even lead to premature death. Ozone can also hurt plants and crops.</string>
	<string name="ozone_effects">Ozone reacts with lung tissue. It can inflame and cause harmful changes in breathing passages, decrease the lungs\' working ability and cause both coughing and chest pains. Ozone air pollution, found at unhealthful levels in nearly all of the nation\'s major urban areas, may particularly affect millions of otherwise healthy Americans who, for currently unknown 1reason, are especially sensitive to it. People who exercise are also more vulnerable to the effects of ozone, suffering symptoms and a reduced ability to breathe at relatively low ozone levels. Ozone pollution, even at low levels, has also been linked to increased hospital admissions and emergency room visits for respiratory problems.</string>

	<string name="co_intro">Carbon monoxide (CO) is an odourless, colourless, poisonous gas that comes mainly from motor vehicles and other combustion exhaust.A gas that comes from the burning of fossil fuels, mostly in cars. It cannot be seen or smelled. Carbon monoxide is released when engines burn fossil fuels. Emissions are higher when engines are not tuned properly, and when fuel is not completely burned. Cars emit a lot of the carbon monoxide found outdoors. Furnaces and heaters in the home can emit high concentrations of carbon monoxide, too, if they are not properly maintained.</string>
	<string name="co_effects">Carbon monoxide interferes with the blood\'s ability to carry oxygen to the brain, heart and other tissues, and it is particularly dangerous for people with existing heart disease, and unborn or newborn children. Carbon monoxide makes it hard for body parts to get the oxygen they need to run correctly. Exposure to carbon monoxide makes people feel dizzy and tired and gives them headaches. Elderly people with heart disease are hospitalized more often when they are exposed to higher amounts of carbon monoxide.</string>
	
	<string name="no2_intro">NO2 is a reddish-brown gas that comes from the burning of fossil fuels. It has a strong smell at high levels. Nitrogen dioxide mostly comes from power plants and cars. Nitrogen dioxide is formed in two ways viz.—when nitrogen in the fuel is burned, or when nitrogen in the air reacts with oxygen at very high temperatures. Nitrogen dioxide can also react in the atmosphere to form ozone, acid rain, and particles. Nitrogen oxides are formed during high temperature combustion processes from the oxidation of nitrogen in the air or fuel. The principal source of nitrogen oxides - nitric oxide (NO) and nitrogen dioxide (NO2), collectively known as NOx - is road traffic, which is responsible for approximately half the emissions in Europe. NO and NO2 concentrations are therefore greatest in urban areas where traffic is heaviest. Other important sources are power stations, heating plants and industrial processes.\nNitrogen oxides are released into the atmosphere mainly in the form of NO, which is then readily oxidized to NO2 by reaction with ozone. Elevated levels of NOx occur in urban environments under stable meteorological conditions, when the air mass is unable to disperse. Whereas nitrogen dioxide (NO2) participates in the formation of ozone, nitrogen oxide (NO) destroys ozone to form oxygen (O2) and nitrogen dioxide (NO2). For this reason, ozone levels are not as high in urban areas (where high levels of NO are emitted from vehicles) as in rural areas. As the nitrogen oxides and hydrocarbons are transported out of urban areas, the ozone-destroying NO is oxidized to NO2, which participates in ozone formation.</string>
	<string name="no2_effects">Nitrogen dioxide has a variety of environmental and health impacts. It is a respiratory irritant, may exacerbate asthma and possibly increase susceptibility to infections. In the presence of sunlight, it reacts with hydrocarbons to produce photochemical pollutants such as ozone (see below). In addition, nitrogen oxides have a lifetime of approximately 1 day with respect to conversion to nitric acid. This nitric acid is in turn removed from the atmosphere by direct deposition to the ground, or transfer to aqueous droplets (e.g. cloud or rainwater), thereby contributing to acid deposition.</string>
</resources>
